Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection
circa 1985 - 2011
Center for Brooklyn History
Pinezich, Lyn
Kriaris, Mike (Michael)
Barnes, Brian
Berning, Laura
Blazevic, Zoran
Carbajal, Steven
Carey, Patty
Carr, Nick
Cooke, Andrew D.
Efrat, Guy
Feinman, Kim
Fritz, Jason
Guest, Joe
Jappe, Jule Ann
Kostic, Isabelle
Quiñones, César
Manion, Randy
McGuire, David M.
Nickodem, Michael
Noonan, Robert
Papa, Eric
Price, James
Retzlaff, Julie
Saxe, Andrew
Solomon, Julie
Vangrofsky, Gayle
Turner, Mimi
CBHM.0017
118.42 Linear feet in 24 records cartons, 17 manuscript boxes, 6 half manuscript boxes, 41 oversize flat boxes, and 1 oversize item.
The Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection contains photographs of Brooklyn locations taken by location scouts for film and television projects from the 1980s to 2011. Photographs are taped into folder dossiers based on location and depict apartments, houses, public housing, hospitals, stores, restaurants, bars, warehouses, churches, schools, subway stations, and streets in neighborhoods across Brooklyn.
Scope and Contents
The Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection contains photographs of Brooklyn locations taken by location scouts for film and television projects from the 1980s to 2011. Photographs are taped into folder dossiers based on location and depict apartments, houses, public housing, hospitals, stores, restaurants, bars, diners, warehouses, churches, schools, subway stations, catering halls, funeral parlors, delapidated buildings, stores, bowling alleys, industrial laundries, and streets in neighborhoods across Brooklyn. It represents production scouting for the films Scent of a Woma n (1992), War of the Worlds (2005), American Gangster (2007), Doubt (2008), Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close (2011), among others.
Location scouts' folder titles often include "INT" or "EXT." This indicates when only the interior or exterior of the location was photographed. This was used inconsistently, so not all of the folders have this information.
Folders were often titled with what they would be used for in the context of the movie. For example, locations scouted for The Cowboy Way (1994) were labelled "Derelict Hotel" even if the building scouted was not a hotel or former hotel. This information has been left in the titles of the folder in this finding aid.
When known, further information about the movie a location was scouted for or how the location was categorized can be found in the Scope and Contents note under the individual folder.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged by the archivist into 44 series based on neighborhood:
Series 1: Bath Beach
Series 2: Bay Ridge
Series 3: Bedford-Stuyvesant
Series 4: Bensonhurst
Series 5: Boerum Hill
Series 6: Borough Park
Series 7: Brighton Beach
Series 8: Brooklyn Heights
Series 9: Brooklyn Navy Yard
Series 10: Brownsville
Series 11: Bushwick
Series 12: Canarsie
Series 13: Carroll Gardens
Series 14: Clinton Hill
Series 15: Cobble Hill
Series 16: Coney Island
Series 17: Crown Heights
Series 18: Cypress Hills
Series 19: Downtown Brooklyn
Series 20: DUMBO
Series 21: Dyker Heights
Series 22: East Flatbush
Series 23: East New York
Series 24: Flatbush
Series 25: Fort Greene
Series 26: Gerritsen Beach
Series 27: Gowanus
Series 28: Gravesend
Series 29: Greenpoint
Series 30: Highland Park
Series 31: Kensington
Series 32: Marine Park
Series 33: Midwood
Series 34: Mill Basin
Series 35: Park Slope
Series 36: Prospect Heights
Series 37: Prospect Park
Series 38: Red Hook
Series 39: Sheepshead Bay
Series 40: Sunset Park
Series 41: Vinegar Hill
Series 42: Windsor Terrace
Series 43: Williamsburg
Series 44: Multiple neighborhoods
Historical Note
Location scouting is a part of the pre-production process of making a film or television show and location scouts generally work under the Location Management team. Once the director or producer decides the type of setting they would like for scenes of a movie or TV episode, a location scout will go out to take photographs of places that fit the request or will source a location from their existing database of location photographs. In addition to the images, location scouts collect information on the location, such as owners' contact information, rental prices, limitations of the location, and anything else that might be useful for a director or producer when reviewing the photographs.
Filming on location in New York City became more appealing for the film and television industry after Mayor John Lindsay signed Executive Order 10 in 1966, forming the Mayor's Office of Film, Theatre and Broadcasting. The popularity of filming in real New York locations instead of on a set created the need for a Locations Department.
At the time the photographs in this collection were taken, location scouts created physical dossiers, manila folders taped together to create pages on which the photographs were taped. To show panoramic views, multiple photographs were taken and taped together to create an uninterrupted image. These dossiers were then presented to the Location Manager, the Production Designer, and finally to the Director.
In the late 1990s, a group of New York-based Locations Department workers obtained a storage space in Bayonne, New Jersey where scouting photographs could be donated at the end of a shoot and used by others starting a new project. Part of the collection was moved to a smaller storage space in Bethpage, Long Island in 2010 because digital photography and digital platforms for sharing and storing files was becoming more common. Now, location scout photography is digital and managed and shared digitally.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Lyn Pinezich, 2011. Additional materials gift of Lyn Pinezich and Michael Kriaris, 2021.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Custodial History
These materials were initially stored in a space in New Jersey and managed by Lyn Pinezich and other location managers. The materials were partially gifted to the Brooklyn Historical Society and New-York Historical Society in 2011. The remaining materials were then moved to a smaller storage space on Long Island and finally gifted to the Center for Brooklyn History in 2021.
Related Materials
The New York Historical holds the Film location scouts photograph collection, 1980s-2000s (PR 293), which includes mostly non-Brooklyn locations.
The New Jersey Room at the Jersey City Free Public Library holds location scout photographs of New Jersey locations.
Separated Materials
Folders depicting Manhattan and Queens have been separated from the collection. Folders from New Jersey were transferred to the New Jersey Room at the Jersey City Free Public Library, 2025.
Appraisal
At the time of the original accession in 2011, The New-York Historical Society and the Brooklyn Historical Society decided to break up the collection according to each institution's collecting scope. As a result, parts of the collection relating to Brooklyn are at the Center for Brooklyn History and parts relating to Manhattan and other boroughs are at The New York Historical.
Biographical Note
Lyn Pinezich is a New York-based filmmaker who began as a Location Scout and Location Manager in the late 1980s, working on movies such as Scent of a Woman (1992), Maid in Manhattan (2002), and War of the Worlds (2005). Pinezich then moved into Production Management.
Pinezich is a member of the Directors Guild of America (DGA) and served as Chair of the DGA's Eastern Council for Assistant Directors and Unit Production Managers.
Michael (Mike) Kriaris is a New York City-based location manager who has worked on productions such as The Big Short (2015), Salt (2010), The Cowboy Way (1994). He is a member of the Directors Guild of America.
Color prints (photographs); Restaurants -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Streets -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Bars (Drinking establishments) -- New York (State) -- Kings County; African American churches -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Church buildings; Motion picture theaters -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Clubs -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Parks -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Private schools -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Public Schools -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Brownstone buildings -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Interior views; Exterior views; Manufacturing industries; Hospitals -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Subway stations -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Warehouses -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Public housing -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Bowling alleys -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Storefronts -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Pinezich, Lyn; Kriaris, Mike (Michael)
- Series 1: Bath Beach, circa 1990 - 1995
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1: Bath Beach includes photographs of restaurants and stores in the Bath Beach neighborhood of Brooklyn in the 1990s.
  - Bars: Del Monte, Bath Avenue and 19th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    This folder was categorized under "Bars, Nightclubs."
  - Oriental Manor: 1818 86th Street at Bay 19th Street, circa 1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    This folder was categorized under "Restaurants, Parks, Housing Projects, Hospitals, Apt. Towers, Retirement Homes."
  - EXT Vacant store: Bath Avenue & Bay 29th Street [Best Farm], 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Colonial Mansion, 1933 Bath Avenue & Bay 22nd Street, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    This folder was categorized under "Cafes, Restaurants; Catering Halls; Diners."
- Series 2: Bay Ridge, 1988 - circa 2010
  Series 2: Bay Ridge includes photographs of schools, bars, restaurants, stores, social clubs, apartments, and houses in the Bay Ridge neighborhood of Brooklyn from 1988 to circa 2010.
  - INT/EXT Bar, The 3 Jolly Pigeons bar, 6802 3rd Avenue, Bay Ridge, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Molloy's Bar, 6101 5th Avenue, Bay Ridge, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    This folder was categorized under "Restaurants."
  - Gazebo, 93rd Street and 4th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RR Stars [4th Avenue and 93rd Street], circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kleinfeld and Son, 8206 5th Avenue (corner of 82nd Street), circa 1990 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - EXT Freighter, The Lovcen, Bay Ridge Anchorage, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bay Ridge Post #157, American Legion, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lento's, 70-03 3rd Avenue (at Ovington Avenue), Bay Ridge, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Demolished House, Bay Ridge, 341 92nd Street, between 3rd Avenue and 4th Avenue, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Pet store, Aquarium and Pet World, 7019 3rd Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT House, 31 79th Street (between Shore Road and Narrows Avenue), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT House, 154 79th Street (between Ridge Boulevard and Colonial Road), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT House, 146 79th Street (between Ridge Boulevard and Colonial Road), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT House, 35 79th Street (between Shore Road and Narrows Avenue), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Nightclub, Legacy Nite Club, Bay Ridge, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Mark Lanes, 423 88th Street, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Marco's Apartment (INT), 9115 Colonial Road, #2F, Bay Ridge, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    This location was scouted for The Manchurian Candidate.
  - Marco's Apartment, 6701 Colonial Road between 67th Street and Senator Street, Bay Ridge, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - INT Marco's Apartment 137, Bay Ridge, 8124 Ridge Boulevard at 82nd Street, Apt. D4, Apt. D2, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 255 79th Street (between 3rd Avenue and Ridge Boulevard), 2003 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - INT Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 8124 Ridge Avenue at 83rd Street, Apt. B1, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - INT Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 8124 Ridge Avenue at 83rd Street, Apt. C5, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - INT Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 8124 Ridge Avenue at 83rd Street, Apts. 135 and 136, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 9115 Colonial Road (at 92nd Street and Marine Avenue), 2003 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Marco's Apartment, Bay Ridge, 7721 Ridge Boulevard at 78th Street, Rockwell Court, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - EXT/INT Nightclub: Spectrum, 802 64th Street between 8th and 9th Avenues, Bay Ridge, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - EXT/INT Bowling, Mark Lanes, 423 88th Street (between 4th Avenue and 5th Avenue), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - New Royal Restaurant, 6822 4th Avenue (at Bay Ridge Avenue), Bay Ridge, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - EXT Diner, Narrows Coffee Shop, 10001 4th Ave (between 99th Street and 100th Street), Bay Ridge, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - EXT Hinsch Luncheonette: 8518 5th Avenue at 85th Street, Bay Ridge, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Christ Church Bay Ridge, 7301 Ridge Boulevard (between 73rd Street and 74th Street), circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Visitation Academy, 8902 Ridge Boulevard (between 91st Street and 89th Street), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    This folder was categorized under "Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close Brooklyn Neighborhoods."
  - EXT/INT School, The Bay View School, P.S. 102, 211 72nd Street and Ridge Boulevard, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    This location was originally scouted for Doubt and reconsidered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - Adelphi Academy of Brooklyn, 8515 Ridge Boulevard (between 85th Street and 86th Street), Bay Ridge, circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    This location was scouted for Doubt and considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - EXT Diner: Bridgeview Diner, 9011 3rd Avenue (between 90th Street and 91st Street), Bay Ridge, circa 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - EXT Diner: Cathy's Place, 4th Avenue at 96th Street, Bay Ridge, Brooklyn, circa 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - EXT New Royal Restaurant, 6822 4th Avenue at Bay Ridge Avenue, Bay Ridge, Brooklyn, circa 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Series 3: Bedford-Stuyvesant, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 3: Bedford-Stuyvesant includes photographs of apartments, playgrounds, parks, bars, public housing, and churches in the Bedford-Stuyvesant neighborhood of Brooklyn from circa 1990 to 2011.
  - Franklin Avenue and Park Avenue, storefront, circa 1990 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - INT Sweatshop, Alro Plumbing Specialty Company, 414 Flushing Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Warehouses."
  - EXT Derelict Hotels, Fulton Street at Saratoga Avenue, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    This location was scouted for The Cowboy Way.
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Lot at 412-410 Nostrand Avenue (between Madison Street and Monroe Street), 1993 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Lot at 918-920 Bedford Avenue between Willoughby Avenue and Myrtle Avenue, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Lot at 705-707 Dekalb Avenue between Marcy Avenue andTompkins Avenue (opposite 710 Marcy Avenue), 1993 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, 1668-1670 Broadway between Decatur Street and Covert Street, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, 594 Myrtle Avenue between Classon Avenue and Taafe Place, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel, Howard Avenue at Chauncey Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel, 162 Throop Avenue and Hopkins Street, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - EXT Derelict Hotel, South 6th Street and Broadway, Williamsburg, circa 1990 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - EXT Park, Herbert Von King Park / Tompkins Park (Marcy Avenue and Lafayette Avenue), 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Church, John Wesley Methodist Church, 260 Quincy Street (at Nostrand Avenue), Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - INT Hotel laundry, Best Metropolitan Towel and Linen Supply, 45 Kosciuszko Street, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Decatur Playground, Lewis Avenue, Marcus Garvey Boulevard, between MacDonough Street and Decatur Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Herbert Von King Park AKA Tompkins Park, Lafayette Avenue at Marcy Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Reinaldo Salgado Playground between Patchen Avenue and Ralph Avenue, between Monroe Street and Madison Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Hattie Carthan Playground, Marcy Avenue and Tompkins Avenue, Monroe Street and Madison Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Saratoga Park, Saratoga Avenue and Howard Avenue (between Halsey Street and Macon Street), Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Potomac Playground, Tompkins Avenue (between Halsey Street and Macon Street), Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Putnam Playground, Marcus Garvey Boulevard between Monroe Street and Madison Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - INT Soul Bros, 1215 Fulton Street (between Bedford Avenue and Arlington Place) [The Hut], 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    This location was scouted for American Gangster.
  - INT Soul Bros, Casablanca, 300 Malcolm X Boulevard at MacDonough Street, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Small's Nightclub, Slave Theatre, 1215 Fulton Street between Arlington Place and Bedford Avenue, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - EXT/INT Recording Studio, Hometown Studio, 1235 Bedford Avenue (between Fulton Street and Halsey Avenue), 2004 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - INT Soul Bros, Sugarhill Supper Club, 609-615 Dekalb Avenue at Nostrand Avenue, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Marcy Avenue Projects, circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - George H. Murray Christian Academy, 760 Dekalb Avenue at Tompkins Avenue, Mt. Pisgah Baptist Church, circa 2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - EXT/INT Shop, 1125 Myrtle Avenue at Broadway, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - EXT/INT Task Force, 1000 Gates Avenue at Broadway and Ralph Avenue, Bushwick, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - EXT/INT Task Force, St. John's [the Baptist Roman Catholic Church], Parish Hall, 790 Willoughby Avenue at Lewis Avenue, 2006 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    This folder was categorized under "Auditoriums, Meeting Rooms, Catering Halls, Modern."
  - INT/EXT Convent / Rectory / Church, Convent of the Sisters of Mercy, 273 Willoughby Avenue, between Classon Avenue and Taaffe Place, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - EXT Church, Cornerstone Baptist Church, 574 Madison Street, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    This location was scouted for Doubt and considered for Salt.
  - INT/EXT Church and school, Elim Church and School, 32 Madison Street at Classon Avenue, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - EXT / INT Brooklyn Adult Learning Center, 475 Nostrand Avenue (between Macon Street and Halsey Street), Stuyvesant Heights, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Holding Space, First AME Zion Church, 54 MacDonough Street at Tompkins Avenue, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - EXT Church, First AME Zion Church (Tompkins Avenue at Macdonough Street) and Stuyvesant Heights Christian Church, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - M. W. Enoch Grand Lodge, 423 Nostrand Avenue (at Jefferson Avenue), 2007 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    This location was originally scouted for Doubt and considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - Mount Lebanon Baptist Church, 230 Decatur Street (between Lewis Avenue and Stuyvesant Avenue), Stuyvesant Heights, circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 86 Walworth Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 661 Willoughby Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 175 Kosciusko Street, Bedford-Stuyvesant, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - St. Andrew's Playground, Atlantic Avenue and Kingston Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 105 Franklin Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant, Brooklyn Neighborhood Sample, circa 2010 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. These photographs depict Throop Avenue and MacDonough Street, Interfaith Medical Center (Albany Avenue and Herkimer Street), Tea Cup Cafe, Halsey Street, Macon Street at Marcus Garvey Boulevard, Lewis Avenue, Tin City, Macon Branch of Brooklyn Public Library, Hart Street, Myrtle Avenue, Spencer Street at Dekalb Avenue.
  - EXT "9 Story" Building, 970 Kent Avenue at Dekalb Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Series 4: Bensonhurst, circa 1985 - 1997
  Series 4: Bensonhurst includes photographs of restaurants, movie theaters, bars, and streets in the Bensonhurst neighborhood of Brooklyn in the 1980s and 1990s.
  - Chookie's Luncheonette, 7818 New Utrecht Avenue, Bensonhurst, circa 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pisa Caterers, 86th Street, Chateau Bleu, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    This location was scouted for Goodfellas. This folder was categorized under "Auditoriums, Meeting Rooms, Catering Halls, Modern."
  - Cotillion Caterers [Cotillion Terrace], 18th Avenue, Chateau Bleu, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Manhattan EXT, Loew's Oriental, 18th Avenue and 86th Street, Bensonhurst, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bensonhurst [18th Avenue and 85th Street], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - INT Seth's, Bensonhurst, 1859 Bay Ridge Avenue (69th Street), between 19th Avenue and 20th Avenue, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Bars and Diners."
  - INT/EXT Neighborhood Bar: B66, 6612 New Utrecht Ave at 15th Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Bensonhurst, 86th Street at Bay 32nd Street, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Bensonhurst, New Utrecht Avenue at 80th Street, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - EXT/INT 1644 73rd Street (between New Utrecht Avenue and 17th Avenue), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    This folder was categorized under "Apartments/Lofts."
- Series 5: Boerum Hill, 1995 - circa 2010
  Series 5: Boerum Hill includes photographs of churches, bars, restaurants, offices, apartments, houses, stores, and a jail from 1995 to circa 2010.
  - Meeting hall, Religious Society of Friends, 110 Schermerhorn Street and Boerum Place, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - EXT Bar, 264 Hoyt Street, Hoyt Street and Degraw Street, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 93 Douglass Street, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - INT Office [YWCA of Brooklyn, 30 3rd Avenue], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - INT Amanda's Apartment, 378 State Street (between Bond Street and Hoyt Street), Boerum Hill, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    This location was scouted for Simply Irresistible.
  - INT Amanda Apartment, 157 Hoyt Street, Boerum Hill, circa 2000 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, Marissa's: 160 Smith Street (between Wyckoff Street and Bergen Street), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, Bar Tabac: 128 Smith Street at Dean Street, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - EXT Electronics Store: Discount Jewelry and Photo, Temple Square (Schermerhorn Street at Flatbush Avenue), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - EXT Electronics Store: Atlantic Avenue and 4th Avenue [Proline Electronics], 2002 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn apartment, 293 State Street, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - St. Clair Restaurant, 93 Smith Street at Atlantic Avenue, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - The Baptist Temple, 360 Schermerhorn Street at 3rd Avenue, circa 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - INT townhouse, 273 State Street, circa 2010 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Jail: Brooklyn House of Detention [Brooklyn Detention Complex], 275 Atlantic Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - INT Townhouse, 314 State Street, circa 2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Houses."
- Series 6: Borough Park, circa 1990 - circa 2007